<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="data_name">
        <item>Love Epiphany-Reality Club</item>
        <item>Espresso-Sabrina Carpenter</item>
        <item>Here We Go Again-Ardhito Pramono</item>
        <item>Wish You Were Here-Neckdeep</item>
        <item>Wonderwall-Oasis</item>
        <item>Always-Daniel Caesar</item>
        <item>Gluesong-Beabadoobee</item>
        <item>Talking To The Moon-Bruno Mars</item>
        <item>Mr.Loverman-Ricky Montgomery</item>
        <item>Corduroy Dreams-Rex Orange County</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_desc">
        <item><![CDATA[Well\nIt goes like this\nYou find out you have similar interests\nYou use your finite sense of humor to entertain her\nBut youre always wondering what shell infer\nOh, such complex human nature\n\nOh, shes the best\nYou keep on sending her these hilarious image texts\nAlways on the hunt for what you should send next\nSecond-guessing, and perplexed\nGuess her attentions got you vexed\nWorried youll soon, run out of jеst\n\nBut dont worry about it\nWere just as cluelеss as the rest\nWere all just looking to connect\nWith no idea of what happens next\nProbably alone with nothing left\n\nYou love the way she makes you feel\nYou start to synchronize your meals\nYou compromise, you make some deals\nSwapped excitement for some comfort\nBack where you started\nIts just the same old song and dance\nA safety net or a love trance\n\nYou make them witness promises\nBound by jewels, your happiness\nYour loves just not like how it was\nLiving with these mini-monuments of your love\nBlessings from up above\nBut her focus is not on you\nAnd the love escapes you too\n\nBut dont worry about it\nWere just as clueless as the rest\nWere all just looking to connect\nWith no idea of what happens next\nWhen youre alone, time to reflect\nYou can lose at any time\nTalking bitter about some bullshit at Valentines\nBut baby, well, thats just the game\nAnd maybe youll win just the same\n\nAnd well find love through the ages, as time goes by\nIn your teen years, where love is shy\nLove, in your 20s, when its raw\nFlirty 30, romance has thawed\nRoaring 40, sparks has stopped\nNifty 50, my sex drive drops\nIn the 60s, I need you with me\nWill you spend forever with me, love?]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Now hes thinkin bout me every night, oh\nIs it that sweet? I guess so\nSay you cant sleep, baby, I know\nThats that me, espresso\nMove it up, down, left, right, oh\nSwitch it up like Nintendo\nSay you cant sleep, baby, I know\nThats that me, espresso\n\nI cant relate to desperation\nMy give a fucks are on vacation\nAnd I got this one boy\nAnd he wont stop calling\nWhen they act this way\nI know I got em\n\nToo bad your ex dont do it for ya\nWalked in and dream came trued it for ya\nSoft skin and I perfumed it for ya\nI know I Mountain Dew it for ya\nThat morning coffee, brewed it for ya\nOne touch and I brand newed it for ya\n\nNow hes thinkin bout me every night, oh\nIs it that sweet? I guess so\nSay you cant sleep, baby, I know\nThats that me, espresso\nMove it up, down, left, right, oh\nSwitch it up like Nintendo\nSay you cant sleep, baby, I know/nThats that me, espresso\n\nIs it that sweet? I guess so\n\nIm working late cause Im a singer\nOh, he looks so cute wrapped around my finger\nMy twisted humor, make him laugh so often\nMy honey bee, come and get this pollen\n\nToo bad your ex dont do it for ya\nWalked in and dream came trued it for ya\nSoft skin and I perfumed it for ya\nI know I Mountain Dew it for ya\nThat morning coffee, brewed it for ya\nOne touch and I brand newed it for ya\n\nNow hes thinkin bout me every night, oh\nIs it that sweet? I guess so\nSay you cant sleep, baby, I know\nThats that me, espresso\nMove it up, down, left, right, oh\nSwitch it up like Nintendo\nSay you cant sleep, baby, I know\nThats that me, espresso\n\nHe is thinkin bout me every night, oh\nIs it that sweet? I guess so\nSay you cant sleep, baby, I know\nThats that me, espresso\nMove it up, down, left, right, oh\nSwitch it up like Nintendo\nSay you cant sleep, baby, I know\nThats that me, espresso\n\nIs it that sweet? I guess so\nThats that me, espresso]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[So here we go again I kissed that girl again\nBut suddenly it must come to an end\nStop smiling you know you are so annoying\nYour chicks your lips your hips are little tempting\nIf she really finds out Ill be dead man walking\n\nYour eyes are blue\nSo good to be true\nI just cant stop thinking about you oh\nThough were a far apart\nYou are still my best bud\n\nSo here we go again I fall in love again\nPlease dont tell that were gonna be friend\nYour love is sweet as honey in the spring\nRomantic places you will be the clue\nThis time love youll always in my dream\n\nIts early too early\nIt comes too early\nIts easy to remember\nBut so hard to forget\n\nOh here we go again I kissed that girl again\nThen suddenly it must come to an end\nStop smiling you know youre so annoying\nYour chicks your lips your hips are little tempting\n\nIf she really finds out Ill be dead man walking\nIIm just a fan\nLiving my fantasy\nFalling in love with the girl I cant see\n\nFly miles away\nWith all my dignity\nSaving all my fireworks\nWill you ever notice me\nWill you ever notice me]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Take it slow, tell me all how youve grown\nJust for me, could we all reminisce\nBetter yet, heres a pen, make a list\nFill it full with all the things Ive missed\n\nCause I can barely drive past the school without stopping to think of you\nAnd how we used to act the fool\nBut worst of all, I wish Id called at least a thousand times or more\nJust to hear what Ive been missing\n\nIf a picture is all that I have\nI can picture the times that we wont get back\nIf I picture it now, it dont seem so bad\nEither way, I still wish you were here\nDont say everythings meant to be\nCause you know its not what I believe\nCant help but think that it shouldve been me\nEither way, I still wish you were here\n\nThinking back on the days where we all used to say\nI know anywheres better than here\nIn the back of the class where we grew up too fast\nLiving life like theres nothin to fear\nBut the ice on the road, driving home all alone\n\nSinging along to a song from three summers ago\nThe one that made you remember it\nNow Ill always remember it (Ill always remember it)\nAs the song that your life ended with\n\nIf a picture is all that I have\nI can picture the times that we wont get back\nIf I picture it now, it dont seem so bad\nEither way, I still wish you were here\nDont say everythings meant to be\nCause you know its not what I believe\nCant help but think that it shouldve been me\nEither way, I still wish you were here\n\nAnd they say youre in a better place (they say youre in a better place)\nBut a better place is right here with me\nYeah, they say youre in a better place (they say youre in a better place)\nToo bad its not what I believe\n\nCause a picture is all that I have\nTo remind me that youre never comin back\nIf I picture it now it just makes me sad\nAnd right now I just wish you were here\nDont say everythings meant to be\nCause you know its not what I believe\nCant help but think that it shouldve been me\nIn the end, I just wish you were here\n\nYeah, they say youre in a better place (they say youre in a better place)\nEither way, I still wish you were here\nDont say youre in a better place (they say youre in a better place)\nIn the end, I just wish you were here]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Today is gonna be the day that theyre gonna throw it back to you\nAnd by now, you shouldve somehow realised what you gotta do\nI dont believe that anybody feels the way\nI do about you now\n\nAnd backbeat, the word is on the street that the fire in your heart is out\nIm sure youve heard it all before, but you never really had a doubt\nI dont believe that anybody feels the way I do about you now\n\nAnd all the roads we have to walk are winding\nAnd all the lights that lead us there are blinding\nThere are many things that I would like to say to you, but I dont know how\n\nBecause maybe\nYoure gonna be the one that saves me\nAnd after all\nYoure my wonderwall\n\nToday was gonna be the day, but theyll never throw it back to you\nAnd by now, you shouldve somehow realised what youre not to do\nI dont believe that anybody feels the way I do about you now\n\nAnd all the roads that lead you there were winding\nAnd all the lights that light the way are blinding\nThere are many things that I would like to say to you, but I dont know how\n\nI said maybe\nYoure gonna be the one that saves me\nAnd after all\nYoure my wonderwall\n\nI said maybe (I said maybe)\nYoure gonna be the one that saves me\nAnd after all\nYoure my wonderwall\n\nI said maybe (I said maybe)\nYoure gonna be the one that saves me (saves me)\nYoure gonna be the one that saves me (saves me)\nYoure gonna be the one that saves me (saves me)]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Baby, baby\nThere will always be a space for you and me\nRight where you left it\nAnd just maybe\nEnough time will pass\nWell look back and laugh\nJust dont forget it\n\nAnd maybe Im wrong\nFor writing this song\nLosing my head over you\n\nAnd Ill be here\nCause we both know how it goes\nI dont want things to change\nI pray they stay the same always\nAnd I dont care\nIf youre with somebody else\nIll give you time and space\nJust know Im not a phase\nIm always, ways, ways\nAlways, ways, ways\n\nIm always, ways, ways\n\nPretty lady, used to walk with me\nDown Bloor street, oh, what a time\nAnd I still remember the fussin, the fightin, the fuckin, the lyin\nIts all fine, youll always be mine\n\nAnd maybe Im wrong (hey, babe, you could)\nFor writing this song (write me a song)\nLosing my head over you\n\nAnd Ill be here\nCause we both know how it goes\nI dont want things to change\nI pray they stay the same always\nAnd I dont care\nIf youre with somebody else\nIll give you time and space\nJust know Im not a phase\nIm always, ways, ways\nAlways, ways, ways\nIm always, ways, ways\n\nAlways, can count on it sure as the stars in the sky\nAlways, you can count on it sure as the stars in the sky\nAlways, my love for you aint goin nowhere\nAlways, I will be here]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Ive never known someone like you\nTangled in love, stuck by you from the glue\nDont forget to kiss me or else youll have to miss me\nI guess Im stuck forever by the glue, oh, and you\n\nYouve been hiding in plain sight, and it appeared, oh I know\nLoving you once only feels wrong, I need you\nI always knew Id find you, to be here is worth the wait to\nIm not lying when I say, Ive been stuck by the glue onto you\n\nIve been stuck by glue\nRight onto you\nIve been stuck by glue\n\nIve never known\nIve never known someone like you\nIve never known\nIve never known someone like you]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[I know youre somewhere out there\nSomewhere far away\nI want you back, I want you back\n\nMy neighbors think Im crazy\nBut they dont understand\nYoure all I had, youre all I had\nAt night, when the stars light up my room\nI sit by myself\n\nTalking to the moon\nTrying to get to you\n\nIn hopes youre on the other side talking to me too\nOr am I a fool who sits alone talking to the moon?\nOh-oh\n\nIm feeling like Im famous, the talk of the town\nThey say Ive gone mad\nYeah, Ive gone mad\nBut they dont know what I know\nCause when the sun goes down, someones talking back\nYeah, theyre talking back, oh\n\nAt night, when the stars light up my room\nI sit by myself\n\nTalking to the moon\nTrying to get to you\n\nIn hopes youre on the other side talking to me too\nOr am I a fool who sits alone talking to the moon?\n\nAh-ah, ah-ah, ah-ah\nDo you ever hear me calling?\n(Ah-ah, ah-ah, ah-ah) oh-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh\n\nCause every night, Im talking to the moon\nStill trying to get to you\n\nIn hopes youre on the other side talking to me too\nOr am I a fool who sits alone talking to the moon?\nOh-oh\n\nI know youre somewhere out there\nSomewhere far away]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Im headed straight for the floor\nThe alcohol served its tour\nAnd its headed straight for my skin\nLeaving me daft and dim\n\nIve got this shake in my legs\nShaking the thoughts from my head\nBut who put these waves in the door?\nI crack and out I pour\n\nIm Mr. Loverman\nAnd I miss my lover, man\nIm Mr. Loverman\nOh, and I miss my lover\n\nThe ways in which you talk to me\nHave me wishin I were gone\nThe ways that you say my name\nHave me runnin on and on\n\nOh, Im cramping up\nIm cramping up\n\nBut youre cracking up\nYoure cracking up\n\nIm Mr. Loverman\nAnd I miss my loverman\nIm Mr. Loverman\nOh, and I miss my lover\n\nIve shattered now, Im spilling out\nUpon this linoleum ground (Mr. Loverman)\nIm reeling in my brain again\nBefore it can get back to you (Mr. Loverman)\nOh what am I supposed to do without you?\n\nIm Mr. Loverman\nAnd I miss my lover, man (I miss my lover)\nIm Mr. Loverman (oh-oh)\nOh, and I miss my lover (Mr. Loverman)\n\nIm Mr. Loverman (oh-oh)\nAnd I miss my loverman\nIm Mr. Loverman\nAnd I miss my lover]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[How could I ignore you?\nTrust me, I adore you\nWere swimmin through our dreams\nKiss me in the shower\nFor a couple hours\nThough were only sixteen\nAnd sit down beside me\nDont call me daddy\nCause thats just fuckin weird\nPromise that youll stay here\nYou and I can lay here\nUntil the end of time\n\nBut girl\nWell, dont you worry bout me\nIt aint new to me\nFeeling this lonely, darling\nGirl, dont worry bout me\nBut if youre ever unhappy\nThen maybe, baby, I must let you go\nLet you go\n\nBaby, now its best here\nTo lay me down and rest here\nLets dream of corduroy\nWork for what you love to do\nAnd I will watch right over you\nWith your heart, Ill never toy\nAnd youre the other half of me\nDream and sleep and laugh with me\nSave me from myself\nSee Im a fucking basket-case\nUntil Im able to see your face\nYou saved me from myself\n\nBut girl\nDont worry bout me\nCause it aint new to me\nFeeling this lonely\nDarling, baby, girl\nDont worry bout me\nCause if youre ever unhappy\nIf youre ever unhappy\nIf youre ever, ever unhappy\nThen maybe\nMaybe, baby, I must let you go]]></item>
    </string-array>

    <integer-array name="data_img">
        <item>@drawable/realityclub</item>
        <item>@drawable/espresso_sabrina</item>
        <item>@drawable/ardhito</item>
        <item>@drawable/neckdeep</item>
        <item>@drawable/oasis</item>
        <item>@drawable/daniel</item>
        <item>@drawable/gluesong_beabadoobee</item>
        <item>@drawable/bruno_mars</item>
        <item>@drawable/ricky</item>
        <item>@drawable/roc</item>
    </integer-array>

    <integer-array name="data_audio">
        <item>@raw/love_epiphany</item>
        <item>@raw/espresso</item>
        <item>@raw/here_we_go_again</item>
        <item>@raw/wish_you_were_here</item>
        <item>@raw/wonderwall</item>
        <item>@raw/always</item>
        <item>@raw/glue_song</item>
        <item>@raw/bruno_mars</item>
        <item>@raw/mr_loverman</item>
        <item>@raw/corduroy_dreams</item>
    </integer-array>
</resources>